<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on MMUC</title>
    <link>http://johnnyjanzen.github.io/mmucan/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on MMUC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://johnnyjanzen.github.io/mmucan/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer</title>
      <link>http://johnnyjanzen.github.io/mmucan/post/2016-02-18-prayer-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://johnnyjanzen.github.io/mmucan/post/2016-02-18-prayer-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pray for Wes and Kim Janzen, your Canadian Music Mission Ukraine Canada missionaries to Ukraine, that we would be faithful to the calling that we have received from the Lord.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pray that our team will be led of the Holy Spirit, and recognize God working, that we may join Him.  While doors are now open to serve in Ukraine, we do not take this for granted.  Pray for open hearts, that listeners will be open and receptive to the gospel of Jesus Christ.  Pray for our friendship-evangelism concert events and Wes as he conducts and speaks. Pray for Kim as she teaches literally hundreds, each week.  Pray for discernment in friendships, invitations and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pray for clarity and boldness.  Pray that our strength would be only in the Lord, and that we might “fearlessly make known the mystery of the gospel” (Ephesians 6:19).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pray that the gospel will “spread rapidly and be honoured wherever it goes &amp;hellip; “ (II Thessalonians 3:1).  Pray for strong and clear singing voices.  Pray for members of the Kyiv Symphony Orchestra and Chorus.  Pray for clarity of mind.  Pray for health, strength and stamina, which are often attacked by antagonistic spiritual forces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pray for guidance and wisdom.  “We ask God to give you a complete understanding of what He wants to do in your lives and we ask Him to make you wise with spiritual wisdom” (Col 1:9).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pray for protection.  There is an ongoing conflict in Ukraine.  Pray that the Lord will keep our people safe from those who might seek to hurt them.  Pray for safety in travel.  Some of our team members go to places of conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pray for refreshment and rest.  “We also pray that you will be strengthened with His glorious power so that you will have all the patience and endurance you need.  May you be filled with joy”  Col 1:11.  We are normal people who deal with normal challenges, stresses and difficulties.  Missionaries can struggle with these issues and feel somewhat alone, away from family members.  Pray that God will encourage us with the knowledge that others are praying for us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pray for Ukraine.  Pray for peace in the hearts of Ukrainians.  Pray for peace in Ukraine.  Pray for the traumatized people that we serve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pray for our family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pray for our fall 2016 Canadian tour planning.  We look forward to bringing 42 exceptional Ukrainian musicians across Canada, starting in Toronto and ending in Vancouver.  We will again share wonderful music, stories of God’s grace, and the gospel of the Lord Jesus Christ at each concert.  This is our calling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pray for our Music Mission Ukraine Canada board as they give overall leadership to the mission;  Michael Berg, Bill Dyck, Al Mitton, Richard Dodding, Arlene Dodding, John Thiessen, Rita Thiessen, Henry Esau, Lynda Esau, Kim Janzen, Wes Janzen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pray for those who give financially.  Without ongoing financial support the ministries of Music Mission Ukraine Canada would not be possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>